aad.org 2006-09-25

# AAD - Privacy Policy

The American Academy of Dermatology (the Academy) is committed to maintaining the privacy of the personal information of visitors to its sites.  Our policies are designed to disclose the information collected and how it will be used.  This policy applies solely to the information provided while visiting this Web site.  The terms of the privacy policy do not govern personal information furnished through any means other than this Web site (such as by telephone or mail). 

** Email addresses and other personal information  **

Personal information such as postal and e-mail address may be used internally for maintaining member records, marketing purposes and alerting customers or members of additional services available.   Phone numbers may also be used by the Academy when questions about products or services ordered arise.  The Academy will not reveal any information about an individual user to third parties except to comply with applicable law or valid legal process. 

 **Cookies   **

A cookie is a small file stored on the site user’s computer or Web server and is used to aid Web navigation.  Session cookies are temporary files created when a user signs in on the Web site or uses the personalized features (such as keeping track of items in the shopping cart).  Session cookies are removed when a user logs off or when the browser is closed.  Persistent cookies are permanent files and must be deleted manually.  The only persistent cookie used on the aad.org site is created when a user asks to save the user name and password to prevent the need to sign in for each visit.  Tracking or other information collected from this persistent cookie or any session cookie is used strictly for the user’s efficient navigation of the site. 

Information provided on a form (such as registering for the Annual Scientific Meeting) is maintained at the Academy solely for that intended use.  

 **Credit cards   **

All credit card transactions are conducted over a secure socket layer connection.  Credit card information is not stored on the server or re-used in any manner.  Only authorized personnel with specific identification and passwords can access credit card information solely for the purpose of performing adjustments or refunds at the customer’s request. 

 **Links   **

This site may contain links to other sites.  The Academy is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.  The user will know when he is leaving aad.org because a different browser window will open. 

 **Children   **

This Web site is not designed or intended to attract children under the age of13 except for the section entitled “Kid’s Connection”.  The Academy does not collect personal information from anyone it actually knows is under the age of 13. 

The Academy welcomes your feedback.  If you have questions or comments about this site, please contact us at [_info@aad.org_](mailto:info@aad.org).
